<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>TecSorocabana - eventos</title><link href="/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="/feeds/eventos.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>/</id><updated>2018-09-01T00:00:00-03:00</updated><entry><title>Coding Dojo Python Set/2018</title><link href="/eventos/coding-dojo-python-092018.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-09-01T00:00:00-03:00</published><updated>2018-09-01T00:00:00-03:00</updated><author><name>Comunidade</name></author><id>tag:None,2018-09-01:/eventos/coding-dojo-python-092018.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Coding Dojo de Python no Space. Setembro/2018&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Eai sabe programar?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Se você sabe programar é bem vindo, se você não sabe É MAIS BEM VINDO AINDA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Neste encontro faremos uma dinâmica chamada Coding Dojo. Não sabe o que é um
Coding Dojo leia este texto explicativo:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/python-sorocaba/coding-dojo#o-que-%C3%A9-um-coding-dojo"&gt;O que é Coding Dojo?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bora lá programar!?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inscreva-se: &lt;a href="https://www.meetup.com/Grupy-SP/events/253769164/"&gt;Grupy-SP Coding Dojo Python
Sorocaba&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>Linux Developer Conference Brazil 2018</title><link href="/eventos/linux-dev-conf-br-082018.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-08-25T00:00:00-03:00</published><updated>2018-08-25T00:00:00-03:00</updated><author><name>Comunidade</name></author><id>tag:None,2018-08-25:/eventos/linux-dev-conf-br-082018.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;We are proud to announce the second edition of Linux Developer Conference Brazil. linuxdev-br is a conference born to be a meeting point for communities developing Free and Open Source Software (FOSS) projects that constitute the Core of modern Linux systems, be it in smartphones, tablets, TVs, cars or in the Cloud. A space to connect developers, enthusiasts and companies and to foster both the development of the communities and the Brazilian FOSS market.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Linux Developer Conference Brazil is an international meeting point in Brazil for the community developing Free and Open Source Software (FOSS) for the Core of Linux systems and it myriad of platforms – mobile, TVs, cars, home appliances, IoT, Cloud and others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By providing a place for developers, enthusiasts and companies to connect, we intend not only to help grow the FOSS community and market in Brazil, but also forge a link between the Brazilian community and the rest of the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe that in order to grow a strong upstream community in Brazil, our industry needs to play an important role in understanding FOSS values and its benefits to product development – be it the freedom of choosing which software to use, faster time to market or more secure software stacks. Inviting companies to the conference and educating them on how to be FOSS citizens is one of our core values.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moreover, the conference focus is exclusively towards upstream contributions to FOSS projects. Getting players in the global market to understand FOSS values and encouraging them to be part of the community will be one of our main challenges in the time to come.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Supporting an environment where all that can flourish is the founding tenet of linuxdev-br!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inscreva-se: &lt;a href="https://www.eventbrite.com.br/e/linux-developer-conference-brazil-registration-43794718181"&gt;Eventbrite Linux Dev Conf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>Encontro GDG Sorocaba Ago/2018</title><link href="/eventos/encontro-gdg-sorocaba-082018.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-08-21T00:00:00-03:00</published><updated>2018-08-21T00:00:00-03:00</updated><author><name>Comunidade</name></author><id>tag:None,2018-08-21:/eventos/encontro-gdg-sorocaba-082018.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Encontro GDG Sorocaba de Agosto&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Estamos retomando nossos encontros mensais.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A partir de Julho, nos encontraremos toda terceira terça-feira do mês na
cantina do SESC Sorocaba.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Venha bater papo, fazer networking e trocar experiências com a gente!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;GDG Sorocaba&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;O Google Developer Group Sorocaba visa agregar os usuários de tecnologias
Google da região de Sorocaba e gerar uma troca de informações, através de
encontros, palestras e eventos. Além de bate papo com Empreendedores,
Investidores e a comunidade em geral.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Se você tem interesse em tecnologias Google, como Android, Google App Engine,
Google Apps, Gmail, Google Maps, Google Maps API, Adwords, Youtube ou qualquer
outra tecnologia, faça parte de nosso grupe e compartilhe idéias.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AVISO: O GDG Sorocaba é um grupo independente de usuários com interesse em
tecnologias Google, e todo conteúdo é inteiramente independente do Google como
empresa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DISCLAIMER: The GDG Sorocaba is an independent user group with an interest in
Google technology and the content from this group is entirely independent from
Google, the corporation.&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry></feed>